Toggle navigation [](https://www.kraftheinzcompany.com/index.html)

Kraft Heinz Site Privacy Notice
-------------------------------

For more information about your California Privacy Rights, please [click here](#californiaprivacy) or scroll down. To opt out of the sale of your personal information, please [click here](#personalinformation) or scroll down.

**Last Updated: September 22, 2023**

Your privacy is important to us. At The Kraft Heinz Company (“Kraft Heinz”, “we”, “us” or “our”), we recognize that visitors to our site may be concerned about the information they provide to us and how we handle that information. This Privacy Notice describes the types of information we collect from and about you when you visit any of our websites where this notice is posted (or the mobile optimized version of the website) (each a “Site”), or when you otherwise interact with us online or in person. This Privacy Notice also explains how we may use and disclose such information, as well as your choices regarding the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information. By using the Site, you agree to the collection, use, and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Notice. If you do not, please do not use the Site.

This Notice applies to Kraft Heinz Sites in the United States and Canada. Kraft Heinz Foods Company is responsible for processing personal information from United States Sites and Kraft Heinz Canada, ULC is responsible for processing personal information from Canadian Sites. For information about how to contact us regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of your personal information, please see below.

Information We Collect
----------------------

### Information You Provide

We collect certain personal information from you when you choose to provide it to us. This may include when you use certain features on our Sites register for an account on one or more of our Sites; make a purchase; sign up for a newsletter or one of our email lists; use our services; participate in a contest, sweepstakes, game, survey, or promotion; request information from us; or otherwise contact us. The personal information we collect may include your name, birthday or age, telephone number, and e-mail address. If you purchase products or services from Kraft Heinz, we may also request your credit/debit card number or other financial information, along with billing information, so we can fulfill your order or request.

We don’t require you to register or provide personal information to view our Sites or access much of its content, such as our many delicious recipes. However, you may be required to provide certain personal information to create a Site account, use certain features, or receive certain offers. For example, when you participate in certain interactive features on our Sites, such as using our recipe exchange, recipe ratings, and product ratings and reviews, you may also provide us with certain information like your e-mail address, nickname, city and state or province of residence, or submit content, such as recipes, ratings, comments, or pictures to the Site.

If you use a third-party login to create your account (such as Facebook Connect or a Google account), sign into our Sites or otherwise link to us, we may receive certain information about you from the third party based on your registration and privacy settings on those third-party websites.

### Loyalty Programs

We may collect your personal information when you choose to join our loyalty programs or promotional campaigns where we aim to enhance your engagement with us. By participating in these programs, we may gather certain information from you. This may include, but is not limited to, your name, contact details, images of receipts, purchase history, referral details, demographic information, preferences, and program activity information such as points earned, rewards redeemed, and engagement with program features. We collect this data through various means, including contests, competitions, receipt scanning, quizzes, gamified experiences, and surveys. The personal information collected through loyalty programs is used to understand our customers’ preferences and needs, to personalize the content we may send to you, to provide customized rewards and offers, to give exclusive access to digital content, products, or experiences to qualified members, to improve our product and services, and to facilitate communications. We may share the personal information collected through these programs with our service providers, as described in the How We Disclose Your Information section below. When you sign up for a loyalty program, we will provide you with information about our program partners and the benefits you can earn by participating in the program. If you submit a deletion request for your personal information, we may be unable to provide you with loyalty program benefits because we need your personal information to process your loyalty program membership and to provide you with the benefits associated with your membership.

We may also collect certain information about you automatically when you visit the Site (see Information Collected by Automated Means below) and from other sources (see Information Collected from Other Sources below) and may combine this information with the information you provide to us.

### Information Collected By Automated Means

We may use cookies, web beacons, pixel tags, log files, or local shared objects (such as Flash cookies), and other technologies to collect certain information about visitors to our Sites, use of our online services, and interactions with our emails and online advertisements, and to allow us to keep track of analytics and certain statistical information which enables us to improve the Sites and provide you with more relevant content and advertising on our Site and other sites.

For example, through these means, we may automatically collect information such as your browser type, operating system, mobile device type and carrier, device identifier, Internet service provider (“ISP”), Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, and the country with which your IP address is associated. We may also collect information about your use of and interaction with the Site, such as the webpages viewed, the date and time you visit the Site, the areas or pages of the Site that you visit, the amount of time you spend viewing or using the Site, the number of times you return to the Site, other click-stream or Site usage data, whether you open, forward, or click-through links, emails, and ads, and other Site usage data. Collecting this information, and linking it with your personal information, for example, helps us to best tailor our Site and enhance your online experience by saving your preferences while you are visiting a particular Site, and to help identify Site features, recipes, advertisements, and offers that may be of particular interest to you.

When you view the site using a mobile device, in addition to the other information we may collect from your actions, we may collect precise geolocation information where you give permission for us to do so.

We also work with third-party advertisers and ad networks to support our Sites. Some of these advertisers and ad networks may use technology such as cookies, web beacons, pixel tags, log files, or local shared objects (such as Flash cookies) to collect information about you when you visit our Site or other websites, including your IP address, ISP, browser type, and whether you have Flash installed, as well as information about your activities on our Sites and on third-party sites. Some of these advertisers and ad networks also may combine this information with other data, such as demographic data received from third parties to assist in tailoring the advertisements displayed to you. These third-party advertisers and ad networks use the information described above to provide you relevant advertisements based on your online behavior, search activities on our Site and on other third-party sites, and demographic information, so that the advertising you see on our Site and other sites more closely reflect your interests and needs. For example, if you search for or browse a recipe or product on our Site, you may see an advertisement from a third-party with information about, or an offer similar to, that for which you were searching or browsing on our Site, or an offer related to a third party whose site you have visited in the past.

### Tracking Options and California Do Not Track Disclosures

Certain parts of our Site require cookies. You are free to set your Internet browser settings to stop accepting new cookies, to receive notice when you receive a new cookie, to disable existing cookies, and to omit images (which will disable pixel tags). On your mobile device, you may also adjust your privacy and advertising settings to control whether you want to receive more relevant advertising. By doing so, you may not be able to use certain features on the Site or take full advantage of all of our offerings. Please refer to your Web browser’s or operating system’s website or “Help” section for more information on how to disable your browser or operating system from receiving cookies or controlling your tracking preferences.

Our system may not respond to Do Not Track requests or headers from some or all browsers. You can learn more about and opt out from receiving third party advertiser cookies by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance and Digital Advertising Alliance of Canada’s opt-out pages [here](https://optout.aboutads.info/) and [here](https://youradchoices.ca/). Without cookies or pixel tags you may not be able to take full advantage of all of Kraft Heinz website features. We adhere to the Digital Advertising Alliance Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising.

### Information Collected From Other Sources

We may obtain information about you from other sources, including commercially available sources, such as data aggregators and public databases, or social networks that you use to connect with us. This information may include your name, demographic information, interests, and publicly-observed data, such as from social media, online activity, and shopping behavior. We may combine this information with the information we collect from you to help us tailor our communications to you and to improve our services and products.

How We Use Your Information
---------------------------

We may use the information we collect from and about you for any of the following purposes:

* To provide products or services you have requested;
* To respond to your comments or questions, or contact you if needed while processing a product or service you requested through our Site;
* To improve our Site, products, and services; develop new products or services; and conduct analysis to enhance current products and services;
* To review the usage and operations of our Site and improve our content, products; and services, including contacting you for your opinions on Kraft Heinz products, services, or websites;
* To send you promotional offers, newsletter, materials, and other communications and information about Kraft Heinz, its portfolio of brands, affiliates, and its partners;
* To provide you with content that is customized to your interests, targeted offers, and advertising on the Sites, on third party sites and media platforms, including in social media, or via email;
* To contact you as necessary when you enter a contest, sweepstakes, or game in order to conduct the promotion (for example, to contact you if you’re a winner);
* To contact you when necessary;
* To use your data in an aggregated non-specific format for analytical and demographic purposes;
* To address problems with the Site or our business;
* To manage our telecommunications networks;
* To protect the security or integrity of the Site and our business;
* As otherwise described to you at the point of data collection; and
* To use and disclose your credit/debit card information only to process payments and prevent fraud.

Additionally, if you use the Site to connect with third-party services you authorize us to use information from and about you, on your behalf, to interact with these third-party services based on your requests.

We may use your identity, contact, technical, usage, account, and profile data, including identity, contact and profile data we have received from data brokers or aggregators, to form a view on what we think you may want or need, or what kinds of products and services may be of interest to you. Combining data from multiple sources in this way is commonly known as “enriching data” or “profile building”. This is how we decide which products, services and offers to include in marketing messages we send. This process may involve automated decision-making to determine which marketing messages will be most meaningful to you based on your interests, preferences, and location. There may also be other instances where we may use your personal information to render a decision based on automated processing of such personal information. If you would not like us to use data from data brokers and aggregators to enrich the data we have collected from you or if you would like to object to automated decision-making or if you would like to submit observations to a member of the personnel of our organization who is in a position to review the decision made by automated means, please contact the Data Privacy Team. We will not use Special Category Data or Sensitive Personal Data in building a profile about you unless you give us your consent to do so.

Note for Quebec residents: If you would like to activate profiling functions, please contact us using the information in the “How to Contact Us” section below.

How We Disclose Your Information
--------------------------------

We do not sell or otherwise disclose personal information about our website visitors, except as described in this Notice. We do not share your personal information with third parties for their own marketing purposes without your consent. For California residents, please see “Your California Privacy Rights” below.

We may disclose the information we collect from and about you in the following ways: (1) among Kraft Heinz brands and subsidiaries for the purposes described above; (2) to our third party service providers we have retained to perform a business, professional or technical support functions for us, including to the extent necessary or desirable to help run promotions, fulfill orders, complete your transaction, or provide customer service (these service providers may have access to personal information about our Site visitors if it is needed to perform their functions for Kraft Heinz, but they are not authorized by Kraft Heinz to use or disclose the information except as necessary to perform services on Kraft Heinz’s behalf or to comply with legal requirements); (3) as necessary to investigate or prevent an actual or suspected crime or injury to ourselves or others, as permitted by law; (4) if we believe that there has been a violation of our Terms of Use or of our rights or the rights of any third party; (5) to respond to judicial process or provide information to law enforcement authorities, regulatory agencies, or other government officials, or otherwise as required by law; and (6) as otherwise described to you in this Notice or at the point of collection.

We share information that we collect from you, such as your email (in hashed form), IP address or information about your browser or operating system, with our identity partners/service providers, including LiveRamp Inc. LiveRamp returns an online identification code that we may store in our first-party cookie for our use in online, in-app, and cross-channel advertising and it may be shared with advertising companies to enable interest-based and targeted advertising. To opt out of this use, please click [here](https://liveramp.com/opt_out/).

In addition, we may share your email address with our service providers, such as media agencies, to send you interest-based advertising on our behalf. We may also share aggregated or de-identified information about you with our advertising and marketing partners, and third-party media platforms, including social media sites, to allow them to send targeted advertising messages and/or conduct analyses on our behalf. If you wish to stop receiving advertising messages from these third parties, please review the “Your Choices” section below. In addition, you may be able to opt out of these ads by clicking on an icon in the ad or through the privacy settings in each social media platform.

We may conduct joint promotions with other companies. We may provide to our promotional partners (and their service providers) certain personal information as necessary to conduct the promotion. We will not share this information with our promotional partners for any other purpose unless you consent to such sharing.

During the normal course of our business, Kraft Heinz may sell or purchase assets. If another entity acquires us or any of our assets, information we have collected about you may be transferred to such entity. In addition, if any bankruptcy or reorganization proceeding is brought by or against us, such information may be considered an asset of ours and may be sold or transferred to third parties. Should a sale or transfer occur, we will use reasonable efforts to try to require that the transferee use personal information provided through the Site in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Notice.

Data processing within the Kraft Heinz group of companies may be done via servers located outside of Quebec, Canada, and the United States. Some of our supplier, advertising, or promotional agency service providers as described above may also be located outside of Quebec, Canada, and the United States. As a result, your personal information may be accessible to regulatory authorities in accordance with the laws of other jurisdictions. If you wish more information about Kraft Heinz policies and practices with respect to the transfer and processing of personal information outside of Canada or the United States, please contact us in any of the ways described in the contact section of this Privacy Notice.

### Links To Other Websites

The Sites may contain links to other websites. We provide these links solely for your convenience and information. Different websites have different privacy practices. You should always check the privacy notice of the specific site you’re visiting to understand the privacy practices associated with that site. We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of third-party websites.

### Public Forums

Any information you may disclose on our Site, in blogs, on message boards, in chat rooms, or on other public areas on the Site or other third-party websites that this Site may link to, becomes public information. Please exercise caution when disclosing personal information in these public areas. Kraft Heinz cannot control the actions of third parties who may view the Site and use publicly-available information for their own purposes.

### Your Choices

You can change your preferences for follow-up contacts by the Kraft Heinz Company, including by limiting how third parties use your email address to send you targeted advertising through social media on our behalf. Please email or call us using the information in the “Contact Us” section below if you wish to change your preferences. Where you wish to unsubscribe from emails or have use of your email address restricted, please allow 10 days for your email to be removed from our marketing database.

### Children's Information

Kraft Heinz is committed to protecting the privacy of children who use our Sites. While most Kraft Heinz Sites are directed to adults, there are a few other Sites intended for use by children under the age of 13. For Services that are directed to children, we may collect, use, and disclose information about you as described in this Privacy Policy. This Children’s Privacy Policy explains our information collection, disclosure, and parental consent practices with respect to information provided by children under the age of 13 (“child” or “children”) and uses terms that are defined in our general Privacy Notice. This policy is in accordance with the U.S. Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”) and the Canadian Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act (“PIPEDA”) and outlines our practices regarding children’s personal information.

Where one of our Services is intended for use by a child under the age of 13, we will obtain consent from the person with parental responsibility before we collect personal information where it is required by applicable laws and regulations.

If you are a child under the age of 13, you should review the terms of this Privacy Notice with your parent or guardian to make sure you understand and accept them. If we discover that we have collected personal information from a child without consent from a parent or guardian where such consent should have been obtained, we will delete that personal information as soon as practical. Access to certain parts of the Kraft Heinz websites and/or eligibility to receive prizes, samples or other rewards are generally limited to users over a certain age.

We sometimes use your personal information to carry out age verification checks and enforce any such age restrictions.

### How We Protect and Retain Your Information

The security of your information is important to us. We have taken certain administrative, technical, and physical steps to safeguard the information we collect from and about our customers and Site visitors against unauthorized use, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. While we make every effort to help ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee our security measures.

Personal information is maintained on our servers or those of our service providers and is accessible to authorized employees, representatives and agents who require access for the purposes described in this notice. We retain personal information in accordance with our record retention policies. Retention periods are set taking into account the purpose for which the personal information was collected, applicable legal requirements, and our legitimate need to retain business records for reasonable periods.

### Updates To This Privacy Notice

We may change or update all or certain portions of this Privacy Notice at any time. When we do, we will post the revised Privacy Notice on the Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of the revised Privacy Notice means you accept these changes. Please check back from time to time so you are aware of any changes or updates to the notice. If we make any material changes, we will provide appropriate notice to you. We will indicate the notice’s effective date on the first page of the notice.

### Your Rights

Depending on the jurisdiction and the Data Protection Laws applicable to you, you may have one or more of the following rights:

**Right to access:** The right to confirm whether we are processing your personal information and to access such personal information.

**Right to correct:** The right to request correction to inaccuracies in your personal information.

**Right to delete:** The right to request deletion of personal information provided by or obtained about you.

**Right to Opt-Out of Certain Processing:** Certain opt-out rights such as opt out of the processing of your personal information for purposes of (i) targeted advertising, (ii) the sale of personal data, or (iii) profiling in furtherance of decisions that produce legal or similarly significant effects on you.

**Right to Portability:** The right to obtain a copy of your personal information in a portable and common file format.

**Right to Non-Discrimination:** The right not to receive discriminatory treatment for exercising your privacy rights described here.

**Right to Appeal:** The right to appeal a decision regarding your consumer privacy requests by contacting us via email.

You may also have the right to withdraw your consent to the communication or use of your Personal Information. Where Kraft Heinz has asked for your consent to process Personal Information and that consent is withdrawn, we will not process that Personal Information further but may not be able to continue providing the goods or services for which the Personal Information was sought.

### How to Exercise Your Rights

If you would like to exercise the rights set out above, please submit a consumer request to us via:

* Email at: [USprivacy@kraftheinz.com](mailto:USprivacy@kraftheinz.com) (for US residents) or [CanadaPrivacy@kraftheinz.com](mailto:CanadaPrivacy@kraftheinz.com) (for Canadian residents)
* Webform [here](https://privacyportal-uk.onetrust.com/webform/a78fbccf-09e8-4fde-ad47-919d8ad6536f/d62b76a5-2053-4b9d-90b7-376c7e408c91)
* Phone at: 1-855-634-1984

A verifiable consumer request must provide us adequate information to allow us to (1) reasonably verify that you are the individual whose personal information we collected (or an authorized representative) and (2) to understand your request so that we can process and respond to it. You may submit verifiable consumer requests on behalf of your minor children.

Depending on where you live, you may have the right to appeal a decision regarding your consumer privacy request by contacting us via email at the address provided above.

### How To Contact Us

**For U.S. residents**, if you have any questions about this Privacy Notice, you can contact us at:  
  
The Kraft Heinz Company  
200 E. Randolph St.  
Chicago, IL 60601  
Attention: Consumer Relations  
1-800-543-5335  
9 a.m. - 5 p.m. Eastern Time, Monday through Friday, excluding holidays.  
Or send us an [e-mail](mailto:USprivacy@kraftheinz.com). We would be happy to answer your questions or hear your concerns.

**For Canadian residents**, if you have any questions or concerns about our Privacy Notice, would like to make a complaint about our personal information handling practices, wish to request access to or correction of your personal information, or request that your personal information be deleted, you can contact us by writing to our Privacy Officer:  
  
Mary George  
Kraft Heinz Canada Privacy Officer  
Kraft Heinz Canada ULC.  
207 Queens Quay West Suite 700  
Toronto ON, M5J 1A7 Canada  
You can also reach our Privacy Officer by [e-mail](mailto:canadaprivacy@kraftheinz.com)  
Or call us at 1-800-567-KRAFT (9 a.m.-9 p.m. Eastern Time, Monday through Friday.)  
We would be happy to answer your questions or hear your concerns.

California Privacy Notice
-------------------------

**Date Last Updated: September 22, 2023**

Your privacy is important to us. This California Privacy Notice supplements our Website Privacy Notice and describes the categories of personal information we collect from and about California residents when you visit any of our websites where this notice is posted (or the mobile optimized version of the website) (each a “Site”), or when you otherwise interact with us online or in person. This Privacy Notice also provides details on sources of collection of personal information, the purposes for which we collect and use such information, how we may use and disclose it, and your ability to control certain uses of it. Please review our Website Privacy Notice for additional information about how we use your personal data. When we use words like "sell,” “share,” “third party,” and “service provider”, which are defined in the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018, as amended (“CCPA”) and California Consumer Privacy Act Regulations (“Regulations”), those definitions apply to this California Privacy Notice.

Information We Collect
----------------------

### Information You Provide

We collect certain personal information from you when you choose to disclose it with us and from the sources as explained below in the Sources of Personal Information section. The personal information we collect from you can vary depending on the nature of your interaction with us and may have included the following in the preceding 12 months:

* Identifiers, such as real name, postal address, IP address, email address, account name, social media account name;
* Characteristics of protected classification under California or federal law, such as age, gender, race, or ethnic background;
* Commercial information, such as records of products or services purchased, obtained, or considered; and purchase histories;
* Internet or other electronic network activity information, such as page views, Site browsing history, information about your interaction with our Site;
* Professional or employment-related information, such as profession, job title, industry of employment, or honorific;
* Education information, such as level of degree obtained; and
* Inferences that may be drawn from the information identified above.

We only collect sensitive personal information on the basis of one or more of the following:

* you have given consent to the collection; and/or
* where the collection is manifestly made public by you.

### Sources of Personal Information

As described in the Website Privacy Notice above, when we collect these categories of personal information, we may collect it directly from you or automatically when you visit the Site, or otherwise interact with us online or in person, or from other sources and may combine this information with the information you provide to us. For detailed information about the categories of sources, please review the Information We Collect section in the Website Privacy Notice.

### Purposes for Collection and Use

We collect and use your personal information for business or commercial purposes that may include providing you with products and services, site improvement, data analysis and security, marketing and communication, and as otherwise described to you at the point of data collection. Please review the How We Use Your Information section under the Website Privacy Notice for detailed information.

### Data Retention Period

We will retain your Personal Information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Notice unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by applicable law for legal, auditing, or compliance purposes.

### Tracking Options and California Do Not Track Disclosures

Certain parts of our Site require cookies. You are free to set your Internet browser settings to stop accepting new cookies, to receive notice when you receive a new cookie, to disable existing cookies, and to omit images (which will disable pixel tags). On your mobile device, you may also adjust your privacy and advertising settings to control whether you want to receive more relevant advertising. By doing so, you may not be able to use certain features on the Site or take full advantage of all of our offerings. Please refer to your Web browser’s or operating system’s website or “Help” section for more information on how to disable your browser or operating system from receiving cookies or controlling your tracking preferences.

Our system may not respond to Do Not Track requests or headers from some or all browsers. You can learn more about and opt-out from receiving third party advertiser cookies by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out page [here](https://optout.aboutads.info/). We adhere to the Digital Advertising Alliance Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising.

How We Use and Share Your Information
-------------------------------------

We use your personal information for business and commercial purposes as described in the Website Privacy Notice. We may disclose the information we collect from and about you in the following ways: (1) among Kraft Heinz brands and subsidiaries; (2) to our service providers we have retained to perform business, professional or technical support functions for us, including to the extent necessary or desirable to help run promotions, fulfill orders, complete your transaction, or provide customer service as described below (these service providers may have access to personal information about our Site visitors if it is needed to perform their functions for Kraft Heinz, but they are not authorized by Kraft Heinz to use or disclose the information except as necessary to perform services on Kraft Heinz’s behalf or to comply with legal requirements); (3) as necessary to investigate or prevent an actual or suspected crime or injury to ourselves or others, as permitted by law; (4) if we believe that there has been a violation of our Terms of Use or of our rights or the rights of any person or company; (5) to respond to judicial process or provide information to law enforcement authorities, regulatory agencies, or other government officials, or otherwise as required by law; and (6) as otherwise described to you at the point of collection.

### Disclosure, Sale, or Share of Personal Information

The CCPA requires us to make specific disclosures regarding our personal information sharing practices. In the last 12 months, we may have disclosed the following categories of personal information to the following categories of recipients, as shown in the table below.

We do not sell your personal information to third parties, in the traditional or common sense understanding of the word "sell." Please note, however, some disclosures below may be interpreted to constitute a “sale” under the CCPA. The column titled "Categories of Third Parties With Whom We Share Personal Information" below describes sharing with third parties for cross-context behavioral advertising.

| **CATEGORIES OF PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTED** | **CATEGORIES OF RECIPIENTS TO WHOM WE DISCLOSE PERSONAL INFORMATION FOR A BUSINESS PURPOSE** | **CATEGORIES OF THIRD PARTIES WITH WHOM WE SHARE PERSONAL INFORMATION** |
| --- | --- | --- |
| **Identifiers, such as real name, postal address, IP address, email address, account name, social media account name;** | Kraft Heinz brands and subsidiaries; service providers, including our marketing, advertising, and media partners; internet service providers; data analytics providers; advertising and marketing networks; social networks; and operating systems and platforms. | Kraft Heinz subsidiaries (such as Primal Kitchen); advertising and marketing networks; social networks; and marketing, advertising, and media partners. |
| **Characteristics of protected classification under California or federal law, such as age, gender, race, or ethnic background;** | Kraft Heinz brands and subsidiaries; service providers, including our marketing, advertising, and media partners; internet service providers; data analytics providers; advertising and marketing networks; social networks; and operating systems and platforms. | Kraft Heinz subsidiaries (such as Primal Kitchen); advertising and marketing networks; social networks; and marketing, advertising, and media partners. |
| **Commercial information, such as records of products or services purchased, obtained, or considered; and purchase histories;** | Kraft Heinz brands and subsidiaries; service providers, including our marketing, advertising, and media partners; advertising and marketing networks; internet service providers; data analytics providers; advertising and marketing networks; social networks; and operating systems and platforms. | Kraft Heinz subsidiaries (such as Primal Kitchen); advertising and marketing networks; social networks; and marketing, advertising, and media partners. |
| **Internet or other electronic network activity information, such as page views, Site browsing history, information about your interaction with our Site;** | Kraft Heinz brands and subsidiaries; service providers, including our marketing, advertising, and media partners; advertising and marketing networks; internet service providers; data analytics providers; advertising and marketing networks; social networks; and operating systems and platforms. | N/A |
| **Professional or employment-related information, such as profession, job title, industry of employment, or honorific;** | Kraft Heinz brands and subsidiaries, service providers. | N/A |
| **Education information, such as level of degree obtained;** | Kraft Heinz brands and subsidiaries, service providers. | N/A |
| **Sensitive information, such as precise geolocation when you permit us to collect it; and** | Kraft Heinz brands and subsidiaries, service providers. | N/A |
| **Inferences that may be drawn from the information identified above.** | Kraft Heinz brands and subsidiaries; service providers, including our marketing, advertising, and media partners; advertising and marketing networks; internet service providers; data analytics providers; advertising and marketing networks; social networks; and operating systems and platforms. | Kraft Heinz subsidiaries (such as Primal Kitchen); advertising and marketing networks; social networks; and marketing, advertising, and media partners. |

We do not sell, share, or otherwise disclose personal information about you except as described here.

We do not sell or share your personal information with unaffiliated third parties for their own marketing purposes without your consent. Please see “Your Rights and Choices” below for information on how to opt-out of the sale or sharing of your data.

We do not knowingly sell or share personal information of consumers under the age of 16.

### Business or Commercial Purposes for Disclosure, Sale, or Share to Third Parties

We may disclose personal information we collect from and about you to the recipients, as listed above, for one or more of the following business or commercial purposes:

* To assist us in responding to your comments or questions, or contacting you if needed while processing a product or service you requested through our website;
* To improve our website, products, and services; develop new products or services; and conduct analysis to enhance current products and services;
* To review the usage and operations of our Site and improve our content, products; and services;
* To send you promotional offers, newsletters, materials, and other communications and information about Kraft Heinz, its portfolio of brands, affiliates, and its partners;
* To provide you with content that is customized to your interests, targeted offers, and advertising on the Sites, on third party sites and media platforms, including in social media, or via email, depending on your preferences;
* To contact you as necessary when you enter a contest, sweepstakes, or game in order to conduct the promotion (for example, to contact you if you’re a winner);
* To conduct joint promotions with third-party partners, where such personal information is necessary to conduct the promotion;
* To address problems with the Site or our business;
* To manage our telecommunications networks;
* To protect the security or integrity of the Site and our business;
* As otherwise described to you at the point of data collection; and
* To process credit/debit card information where needed to process payments and prevent fraud.

Additionally, if you use the Site to connect with third-party services you authorize us to use information from and about you, on your behalf, to interact with these third-party services based on your requests.

### Additional Information Regarding Data Sharing and Cookies

We also work with third-party advertisers and ad networks to support our Sites. Some of these advertisers and ad networks may use technology such as cookies, web beacons, pixel tags, log files, or local shared objects (such as Flash cookies) to collect information about you when you visit our Site or other websites, including your IP address, ISP, browser type, and whether you have Flash installed, as well as information about your activities on our Sites and on third-party sites. Some of these advertisers and ad networks also may combine this information with other data, such as demographic data received from third parties to assist in tailoring the advertisements displayed to you. These third-party advertisers and ad networks use the information described above to provide you relevant advertisements based on your online behavior, search activities on our Site and on other third-party sites, and demographic information, so that the advertising you see on our Site and other sites more closely reflect your interests and needs. For example, if you search for or browse a recipe or product on our Site, you may see an advertisement from a third-party with information about, or an offer similar to, that for which you were searching or browsing on our Site, or an offer related to a third party whose site you have visited in the past. To opt-out of sharing your personal information, please see the “Your Rights and Choices” section below.

Notice of Financial Incentive
-----------------------------

We may offer you certain benefits through loyalty programs, coupons, discounts, and similar programs (each a “Program” and, collectively, “Programs”). If you participate in a Program, we may collect personal information from you, such as your name, email address, phone number, and other relevant information. As a result, the Program may constitute a “financial incentive” under California law and may be subject to additional terms and conditions which will be provided to you during the Program sign-up process. You can opt-in to participate in a Program by following the Program registration guidelines. You have the right to withdraw from a Program at any point, subject to applicable law, the Program terms and conditions, and our Privacy Notice, by following the instructions provided. Typically, we do not put a monetary value on your personal information. However, California law requires we provide a valuation of personal information collected in connection with a financial incentive. The value of the personal information you provide while participating in a Program is based upon our reasonable and good-faith estimation of the value of such information, which considers, without limitation, the value and purpose of the Program, associated expenses, the type and usage of the collected personal information, and the number of individuals who participated in the Program.

Your Rights and Choices
-----------------------

You have the right to request that we provide certain information to you about how we collected and used your personal information. Specifically, you have the following rights:  
**Right to Access**: You have the right to request access to categories and specific pieces of personal information about you that we collect, use, disclose, share, and sell. If requested, we will provide you a copy of your personal information we collected as permitted by CCPA.  
**Right to Delete**: In certain circumstances, you have the right to request that we delete personal information that we collect from you, subject to applicable legal exceptions. Upon verifying the validity of a deletion request, we will delete your personal information from our records.  
**Right to Know**: You have the right to know the information that we collect, as defined in the CCPA.

* The categories of personal information we collected about you;
* The categories of sources of personal information we collected about you;
* The business or commercial purpose(s) for which we collected, sold, or shared your personal information; and
* The categories of third parties with which we share your personal information and, where such disclosures were for a business purpose, the personal information categories that each category of third-party recipients received and, where such disclosures were “sales” or “shares”, the personal information categories purchased or received by each category of recipient; and
* The specific pieces of personal information we collected about you.

**Right to Correct**: You have the right to correct inaccurate personal information maintained by us. Upon verifying the validity of the request, we will use commercially reasonable efforts to correct your personal information as directed, taking into account the nature and purpose of maintaining your personal information.  
**Right to Opt-Out of Selling or Sharing of Personal Information**: You have the right to Opt-Out of the selling or sharing of your personal information to third parties (as those terms are defined in the CCPA).  
**Right to Limit the Use and Disclosure of Sensitive Personal Information**: You have the right to limit the use and disclosure of your sensitive personal information. The sensitive personal information we collect about you can be found above in the table above.  
**Right Not to Receive Discriminatory Treatment**: You have the right not to receive discriminatory treatment for exercising your privacy rights described by the CCPA.  

### How to Exercise Your Rights

If you would like to exercise the rights set out above, please submit a verifiable consumer request to us via:

* Email at: [USprivacy@kraftheinz.com](mailto:USprivacy@kraftheinz.com)
* Webform [here](https://privacyportal-uk.onetrust.com/webform/a78fbccf-09e8-4fde-ad47-919d8ad6536f/d62b76a5-2053-4b9d-90b7-376c7e408c91)
* Phone at:1-855-634-1984

A verifiable consumer request must provide us adequate information to allow us to (1) reasonably verify that you are the individual whose personal information we collected (or an authorized representative) and (2) to understand your request so that we can process and respond to it. Please note that only you, or a person registered with the California Secretary of State that you authorize to act on your behalf, may submit a verifiable consumer request for your personal information. You may submit verifiable consumer requests on behalf of your minor children.

Once we have received and verified your request, we will send a confirmation of our receipt of your request and, within 45 days, either a copy of the requested information or confirmation of deletion or correction, as applicable. If, for any reason, we are unable to fulfill your request, we will notify you and provide an explanation.

Do Not Sell or Share My Personal Information
--------------------------------------------

To opt-out of the sale or sharing of your personal information, please call us at 1-855-634-1984, use our Webform [here](https://privacyportal-uk.onetrust.com/webform/a78fbccf-09e8-4fde-ad47-919d8ad6536f/d62b76a5-2053-4b9d-90b7-376c7e408c91) or send an email to [USprivacy@kraftheinz.com](mailto:USprivacy@kraftheinz.com).

Limit the Use and Disclosure of My Sensitive Personal Information
-----------------------------------------------------------------

To limit the use or disclosure of your sensitive personal information, please call us at 1-855-634-1984, use our Webform [here](https://privacyportal-uk.onetrust.com/webform/a78fbccf-09e8-4fde-ad47-919d8ad6536f/d62b76a5-2053-4b9d-90b7-376c7e408c91) or send an email to [USprivacy@kraftheinz.com](mailto:USprivacy@kraftheinz.com).

Kraft Heinz Data Subject Rights Requests
----------------------------------------

Kraft Heinz has compiled the below statistics regarding its Access, Delete and Do Not Sell My Personal Information requests received, fulfilled (in whole or in part), denied between January 1, 2022 and December 31, 2022. Kraft Heinz authenticates requests in accordance with applicable law but does not request consumers provide proof of residence in a given state or territory. Instead, Kraft Heinz actions all requests received which pertain to marketing activities in the United States. Accordingly, the below statistics reflect total numbers of data subject rights requests received from all consumers in the relevant time period.

|     | 2022 |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
|     | Count | Mean No. Days |
| --- | --- | --- |
| **Requests to Know** |     |     |
| Received | 1   |     |
| Complied | 1   | 11  |
| Denied | 0   | \-  |
| **Requests to Delete** |     |     |
| Received | 65  |     |
| Complied | 65  | 19  |
| Denied | 0   | \-  |
| **Requests to Opt-Out** |     |     |
| Received | 570 |     |
| Complied | 570 | 5   |
| Denied | 0   | \-  |

### Shine the Light

If you are a California resident, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits you to request information regarding the disclosure of your personal information by Kraft Heinz to third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. Such requests may be made once per calendar year for information about any relevant sharing in the prior calendar year. We take great pride in the relationship of trust we have built with our consumers over many years and we are dedicated to treating your personal information with care and respect. Pursuant to California Civil Code Section 1798.83(c)(2), Kraft Heinz do not share consumer’s personal information with third parties for direct marketing use unless a customer elects that we do so.

To make such request, please send an email to [USprivacy@kraftheinz.com](mailto:USprivacy@kraftheinz.com) or write to us at:  
The Kraft Heinz Company  
200 E. Randolph St.  
Chicago, IL 60601  
Attention: Data Privacy Team

### Updates To This California Privacy Notice

We may change or update portions of this California Privacy Notice at any time. When we do, we will post the change(s) on the Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to these terms means you accept these changes. Please check back from time to time so you are aware of any changes or updates to the notice. If we make any material changes, we will provide appropriate notice to you. We will indicate the notice’s effective date at the top of the notice.

### How To Contact Us

If you have any questions about this California Privacy Notice, you can contact us at:  
  
The Kraft Heinz Company  
200 E. Randolph St.  
Chicago, IL 60601  
Attention: Data Privacy Team  
Call us at 1-855-634-1984  
9 a.m. - 5 p.m. Eastern Time, Monday through Friday, excluding holidays.  
E-mail us at [USprivacy@kraftheinz.com](mailto:USprivacy@kraftheinz.com). We would be happy to answer your questions or hear your concerns.

* [No Surprises Act Notice](https://www.kraftheinzcompany.com/pdf/NoSurpriseBillingNotice(879514.1).pdf)

© 2024 The Kraft Heinz Company. All rights reserved.
